<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="hello">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
	<string name="app_name">GTUG Widget</string>
	<string-array name="will_rogers_quotes">
		<item>An ignorant person is one who doesn't know what you have just
			found out.
		</item>
		<item>An onion can make people cry, but there has never been a
			vegetable invented to make them laugh.
		</item>
		<item>Ancient Rome declined because it had a Senate; now what's going
			to happen to us with both a Senate and a House?
		</item>
		<item>Be thankful we're not getting all the government we're paying
			for.
		</item>
		<item>Diplomacy is the art of saying 'Nice doggie' until you can find
			a rock.
		</item>
		<item>Don't gamble; take all your savings and buy some good stock and
			hold it till it goes up, then sell it. If it don't go up, don't buy
			it.
		</item>
		<item>Even if you're on the right track, you'll get run over if you
			just sit there.
		</item>
		<item>I belong to no organized party. I am a Democrat.
		</item>
		<item>I never expected to see the day when girls would get sunburned
			in the places they do today.
		</item>
		<item>I was not a child prodigy, because a child prodigy is a child
			who knows as much when it is a child as it does when it grows up.
		</item>
		<item>I'm not a real movie star. I've still got the same wife I
			started out with twenty-eight years ago.
</item>
		<item>Live in such a way that you would not be ashamed to sell your
			parrot to the town gossip.
</item>
		<item>Nothing you can't spell will ever work.
</item>
		<item>On account of being a democracy and run by the people, we are
			the only nation in the world that has to keep a government four
			years, no matter what it does.
</item>
		<item>Our constitution protects aliens, drunks and U.S. Senators.
		</item>
		<item>Politics is applesauce.
</item>
		<item>Take the diplomacy out of war and the thing would fall flat in a
			week.
</item>
		<item>The best doctor in the world is the veterinarian. He can't ask
			his patients what is the matter-he's got to just know.
</item>
		<item>The movies are the only business where you can go out front and
			applaud yourself.
</item>
		<item>The only time people dislike gossip is when you gossip about
			them.
</item>
		<item>There ought to be one day-- just one-- when there is open season
			on senators.
</item>
		<item>There's no trick to being a humorist when you have the whole
			government working for you.
</item>
		<item>This country has come to feel the same when Congress is in
			session as when the baby gets hold of a hammer.
</item>
		<item>We are all here for a spell; get all the good laughs you can.
		</item>
		<item>We can't all be heroes because somebody has to sit on the curb
			and clap as they go by.
</item>
		<item>We don't know what we want, but we are ready to bite somebody to
			get it.
</item>
		<item>Rumor travels faster, but it don't stay put as long as truth.
		</item>
		<item>There is only one thing that can kill the Movies, and that is
			education.
</item>
		<item>The more you read and observe about this Politics thing, you got
			to admit that each party is worse than the other. The one that's out
			always looks the best.
</item>
		<item>The income tax has made more liars out of the American people
			than golf has.</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>
